Bert JW Regeer

Bert JW Regeer Tel: +1-480-264-0039 Email: bertjw@regeer.org

Profile

I am a highly motivated individual, who enjoys working with technology. My strongest point is UNIX/Linux server administration and programming for these platforms. I have extensive experience writing shell scripts to accomplish new tasks. As well as maintaining and working with open source software to do web serving, e-mail and databases. I have also completed network security testing for a university. My interests lie in various different areas, including electronics, hardware and embedded systems. I am going to school for a degree in Software Engineering, computer programming.

I am from the Netherlands, and as such bring a unique perspective to any team. Having lived in and travelled to many countries I am very open to new cultures and ideas. I have resided in the US for the last 9 years, and during that time have met many people that I enjoyed working with.

Skills

Operating Systems	Software	Languages	Databases
Mac OS X	Subversion (svn)	C++	MySQL
FreeBSD	Apache	C	sqlite 3
Linux	Lighttpd	PHP	PostgreSQL
Windows XP	qmail/vpopmail	Python	
Windows 2000	djbdns	C#	
Windows 2003	BIND	Java	
Windows 7	Samba	JavaScript	
Windows 2008	pf (Firewall)	Perl	
Solaris 10/OpenSolaris	Visual Studio	Visual Basic	
	TextMate	PBASIC	
	VMWare	SX/B	
		bash/sh	

Experience

Owner and Founder, Developer; Colossal Dynamics Corporation - 2009 - Current

- » Founder and part owner
- » Software developer for internal applications
- » Client/corporate relationship management
- » On-site work for clients
- » Embedded platform engineer

System Administrator/Web Master; osnn.net - 2002 - current

- » Configure, maintain, secure and administrate FreeBSD and services
- » Tune server resources for the load
- » Migrating live website to new location
- » Monitoring of services for reliability and uptime (SSH, httpd, email)
- » Securing and threat assessment
- » Basic web-master duties/forum moderation

System Administrator; netuse.co.uk - August 2006 - current

- » Configure, maintain, secure and administrate FreeBSD and services
- » Monitoring of services for reliability and uptime (SSH, httpd, email)

- » Shell scripting to backup user data and e-mail
- » 24/7 stand-by, on-call administration
- » Using FreeBSD as a server platform has achieved greater uptime and availability

Website Engineer/Lead Designer (internship); AEC Consultants - 2009 - 2009

- » Design company website
- » Design and build Zend Framework based backend for dynamic content
- » Design and build MySQL based database as a backend

Volunteer worker; Blackhat - July 2009

- » Check people in and provide conference badges
- » Lay network and power cables for the students in the classes
- » Set up wireless nodes for Aruba networks
- » Sell T-Shirts and other Blackhat swag in the Black Hat store

Volunteer worker; Blackhat - August 2008

- » Lay network and power cables for the students in the classes
- » Set up wireless nodes for Aruba networks
- » Direct people to and from lunch and check tickets
- » Sell T-Shirts and other Blackhat swag in the Black Hat store
- » Stuff swag bags

Security Audit; University of Advancing Technology - February 2007 - April 2007

- » General network security audit
- » Finding exploits in intranet web applications (SQL Injections)
- » Pen testing
- » Analyses of network protocols

VPS to server migration; netuse.co.uk - April 2006 - July, 2006

- » Migrated from virtual solution to dedicated server
- » Sendmail to qmail/vpopmail
- » Implement virtual user system with Pure-FTPD and pure-db
- » Shell scripts to maintain users/passwords for virtual users system
- » Migration of all user data with minimal downtime

Projects

These are the projects I am currently involved in, or have been involved in.

Near Space

As a team of 15 students we developed a near space pay-load along with the various science experiments. With a GPS device TNC and a HAM radio on-board we were able to track the near space pay-load using APRS data that was being sent back. After retrieving the pay-load we were able to retrieve the science data along with the pictures that we had taken with a still camera.

Christmas Tree Hack

I worked together with a team of other students at my university to set up an embedded web server running on the parallax PINK system, to control the christmas tree remotely. The PINK talked to an BS2 stamp which in turn controlled a relay box that allowed us to individually turn certain sections of the tree on and off

Education

2006 - 2009, University of Advancing Technology; Tempe, Arizona

Degree: Bachelor of Science: Software Engineering

Major: Computer Programming